[
    {
        "question": "What international city is served by Charles de Gaulle Airport?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US city is the United States Naval Academy located?",
        "answer": "Annapolis, Maryland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only New England state with no Atlantic coastline?",
        "answer": "Vermont"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest country in Africa in terms of land size?",
        "answer": "Algeria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the deepest part of the Atlantic Ocean?",
        "answer": "Milwaukee Deep"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country`s name is derived from the term `hollow land`?",
        "answer": "Holland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country is stereotypically associated with tulips, windmills and clogs?",
        "answer": "Holland"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Albert Canal is located in which country?",
        "answer": "Belgium"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mount Kosciuszko is located in which country?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Caribbean Island of Bonaire is a municipality of what country?",
        "answer": "The Netherlands -- It forms part of the `ABC Islands,` the westernmost island group in the Leeward Antilles."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the coldest temperature measured in the contiguous U.S.?",
        "answer": "Rogers Pass, Montana -- It was -70 degrees Fahrenheit on January 20, 1954."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the coldest temperature recorded in Canada?",
        "answer": "Snag in the Yukon -- The temperature was -81\u00b0 F (-62.8\u00b0 C) In February 1947."
    },
    {
        "question": "Located in Uganda and Tanzania, what is the largest lake in Africa?",
        "answer": "The lake is relatively young \u2014 around 400,000 years old \u2014 and has dried up several times in its history."
    },
    {
        "question": "Japan has over 200 flavors of what popular candy?",
        "answer": "Kit Kat -- Japan`s flavors include strawberry, melon, matcha, soy sauce, corn and green beans."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Brazil?",
        "answer": "Brasilia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country grows the most avocados?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Bangladesh?",
        "answer": "Dhaka"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dhaka is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Bangladesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dhaka is the capital of which Asian country?",
        "answer": "Bangladesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Mauritius?",
        "answer": "Port Louis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Port Louis is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Mauritius"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mauritius is part of which continent?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Pennsylvania town is the birthplace of `Rolling Rock Beer`?",
        "answer": "Latrobe"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city was the oldest university in Scandinavia founded in 1477?",
        "answer": "Uppsala"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is known as the Glass Capital of the World?",
        "answer": "Toledo, Ohio"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the first of November, Spain celebrates `Todos los Santos` which translates to what in English?",
        "answer": "All Saints Day"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lederhosen would be seen on legs in which country?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "`Scotland`s Disgrace` was an attempt to replicate which iconic structure?",
        "answer": "The Parthenon in Athens, Greece -- The attempt was meant as a nod to Edinburg`s reputation as the `Athens of the North.`"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first European nation to have a woman prime minister?",
        "answer": "United Kingdom -- Margaret Thatcher`s Conservative party took power in 1979 making her UK`s Prime Minister."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state is home to America`s first public beach?",
        "answer": "Massachusetts -- Revere Beach, just north of Boston, is considered America`s first public beach."
    },
    {
        "question": "What location was used to film the movie `Jaws`?",
        "answer": "Martha`s Vineyard, Massachusetts"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the western border of San Francisco, California?",
        "answer": "Ocean Beach -- It is a 3.5 mile stretch of beach that runs adjacent to Golden Gate Park."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state has America`s shortest coastline?",
        "answer": "New Hampshire -- Coming in at just 18.57 miles, the state`s beaches may not stretch far, but they do not disappoint."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two states share a border with South Carolina?",
        "answer": "Georgia and North Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is located near Lackland Air Force Base?",
        "answer": "San Antonio"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state can you find permafrost?",
        "answer": "Alaska"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to Petroglyph National Monument?",
        "answer": "New Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is home to Pike Place Market?",
        "answer": "Seattle"
    },
    {
        "question": "The fillet of which fish is used to make `rollmops`?",
        "answer": "Herring"
    },
    {
        "question": "Columbus is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "Ohio"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Nigeria and Gabon?",
        "answer": "Cameroon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Tajikistan and Russia?",
        "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state does the Rio Grande river begin?",
        "answer": "Colorado"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders only Brazil, Argentina, and the Atlantic Ocean?",
        "answer": "Uruguay"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what US state is Dulles International Airport located?",
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many US state capital cities lie on the Mississippi River?",
        "answer": "Two - Baton Rouge and St. Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two US state capitals cities lie on the Mississippi River?",
        "answer": "Baton Rouge and St. Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two rivers does the Nile split into?",
        "answer": "Blue Nile and White Nile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state capital city lies closest to Philadelphia?",
        "answer": "Trenton, New Jersey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vienna is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Austria"
    }
]